<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Command Line Reference on Gloo Docs</title>
    <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Command Line Reference on Gloo Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl/</guid>
      <description> glooctl CLI for Gloo
Synopsis glooctl is the unified CLI for Gloo. Find more information at https://solo.io
Options  -h, --help help for glooctl -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl add - adds configuration to a top-level Gloo resource glooctl create - Create a Gloo resource glooctl delete - Delete a Gloo resource glooctl get - Display one or a list of Gloo resources glooctl install - install gloo on different platforms glooctl proxy - interact with proxy instances managed by Gloo glooctl remove - remove configuration items from a top-level Gloo resource glooctl route - subcommands for interacting with routes within virtual services glooctl uninstall - uninstall gloo glooctl upgrade - upgrade glooctl binary  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl add</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_add/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_add/</guid>
      <description> glooctl add adds configuration to a top-level Gloo resource
Synopsis adds configuration to a top-level Gloo resource
Options  -h, --help help for add --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo glooctl add route - Add a Route to a Virtual Service  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl add route</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_add_route/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_add_route/</guid>
      <description>glooctl add route Add a Route to a Virtual Service
Synopsis Routes match patterns on requests and indicate the type of action to take when a proxy receives a matching request. Requests can be broken down into their Match and Action components. The order of routes within a Virtual Service matters. The first route in the virtual service that matches a given request will be selected for routing.
If no virtual service is specified for this command, glooctl add route will attempt to add it to a default virtualservice with domain &amp;lsquo;*&amp;lsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create/</guid>
      <description> glooctl create Create a Gloo resource
Synopsis Gloo resources be created from files (including stdin)
glooctl create [flags]  Options  -f, --file string file to be read or written to -h, --help help for create -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo glooctl create secret - Create a secret glooctl create upstream - Create an Upstream Interactively glooctl create virtualservice - Create a Virtual Service  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create secret</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_secret/</guid>
      <description> glooctl create secret Create a secret
Synopsis Create a secret
glooctl create secret [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for secret  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  SEE ALSO  glooctl create - Create a Gloo resource glooctl create secret aws - Create an AWS secret with the given name glooctl create secret azure - Create an Azure secret with the given name glooctl create secret tls - Create a secret with the given name  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create secret aws</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_secret_aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_secret_aws/</guid>
      <description> glooctl create secret aws Create an AWS secret with the given name
Synopsis Create an AWS secret with the given name
glooctl create secret aws [flags]  Options  --access-key string aws access key -h, --help help for aws --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;) --secret-key string aws secret key  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  SEE ALSO  glooctl create secret - Create a secret  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create secret azure</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_secret_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_secret_azure/</guid>
      <description> glooctl create secret azure Create an Azure secret with the given name
Synopsis Create an Azure secret with the given name
glooctl create secret azure [flags]  Options  --api-keys strings comma-separated list of azure api key=value entries -h, --help help for azure --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  SEE ALSO  glooctl create secret - Create a secret  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create secret tls</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_secret_tls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_secret_tls/</guid>
      <description> glooctl create secret tls Create a secret with the given name
Synopsis Create a secret with the given name
glooctl create secret tls [flags]  Options  --certchain string filename of certchain for secret -h, --help help for tls --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;) --privatekey string filename of privatekey for secret --rootca string filename of rootca for secret  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  SEE ALSO  glooctl create secret - Create a secret  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create upstream</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream/</guid>
      <description> glooctl create upstream Create an Upstream Interactively
Synopsis Upstreams represent destination for routing HTTP requests. Upstreams can be compared to clusters in Envoy terminology. Each upstream in Gloo has a type. Supported types include static, kubernetes, aws, consul, and more. Each upstream type is handled by a corresponding Gloo plugin.
glooctl create upstream [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for upstream  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  SEE ALSO  glooctl create - Create a Gloo resource glooctl create upstream aws - Create an Aws Upstream glooctl create upstream azure - Create an Azure Upstream glooctl create upstream consul - Create a Consul Upstream glooctl create upstream kube - Create a Kubernetes Upstream glooctl create upstream static - Create a Static Upstream  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create upstream aws</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_aws/</guid>
      <description>glooctl create upstream aws Create an Aws Upstream
Synopsis AWS Upstreams represent a set of AWS Lambda Functions for a Region that can be routed to with Gloo. AWS Upstreams require a valid set of AWS Credentials to be provided. These should be uploaded to Gloo using glooctl create secret aws
glooctl create upstream aws [flags]  Options  --aws-region string region for AWS services this upstream utilize (default &amp;quot;us-east-1&amp;quot;) --aws-secret-name glooctl create secret aws --help name of a secret containing AWS credentials created with glooctl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create upstream azure</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_azure/</guid>
      <description>glooctl create upstream azure Create an Azure Upstream
Synopsis Azure Upstreams represent a set of Azure Functions for a Function App that can be routed to with Gloo. Azure Upstreams require a valid set of Azure Credentials to be provided. These should be uploaded to Gloo using glooctl create secret azure
glooctl create upstream azure [flags]  Options  --azure-app-name string name of the Azure Functions app to associate with this upstream --azure-secret-name glooctl create secret azure --help name of a secret containing Azure credentials created with glooctl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create upstream consul</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_consul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_consul/</guid>
      <description>glooctl create upstream consul Create a Consul Upstream
Synopsis Consul Upstreams represent a collection of endpoints for Services registered with Consul. Typically, Gloo will automatically discover these upstreams, meaning you don&amp;rsquo;t have to create them. However, if upstream discovery in Gloo is disabled, or ACL permissions have not been granted to Gloo to read from the registry, Consul services can be added to Gloo manually via the CLI.
glooctl create upstream consul [flags]  Options  --consul-service string name of the service in the consul registry --consul-service-tags strings comma-separated list of tags for choosing a subset of the service in the consul registry -h, --help help for consul --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;) --service-spec-type string if set, Gloo supports additional routing features to upstreams with a service spec.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create upstream kube</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_kube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_kube/</guid>
      <description>glooctl create upstream kube Create a Kubernetes Upstream
Synopsis Kubernetes Upstreams represent a collection of endpoints for Services registered with Kubernetes. Typically, Gloo will automatically discover these upstreams, meaning you don&amp;rsquo;t have to create them. However, if upstream discovery in Gloo is disabled, or RBAC permissions have not been granted to Gloo to read from the registry, Kubernetes services can be added to Gloo manually via the CLI.
glooctl create upstream kube [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for kube --kube-service string name of the kubernetes service --kube-service-labels strings comma-separated list of labels (key=value) to use for customized selection of pods for this upstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create upstream static</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_static/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_upstream_static/</guid>
      <description>glooctl create upstream static Create a Static Upstream
Synopsis Static upstreams are intended to connect Gloo to upstreams to services (often external or 3rd-party) running at a fixed IP address or hostname. Static upstreams require you to manually specify the hosts associated with a static upstream. Requests routed to a static upstream will be round-robin load balanced across each host.
glooctl create upstream static [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for static --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;) --service-spec-type string if set, Gloo supports additional routing features to upstreams with a service spec.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl create virtualservice</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_virtualservice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_create_virtualservice/</guid>
      <description>glooctl create virtualservice Create a Virtual Service
Synopsis A virtual service describes the set of routes to match for a set of domains. Virtual services are containers for routes assigned to a domain or set of domains. Virtual services must not have overlapping domains, as the virtual service to match a request is selected by the Host header (in HTTP1) or :authority header (in HTTP2). The routes within a virtual service</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl delete</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_delete/</guid>
      <description> glooctl delete Delete a Gloo resource
Synopsis Delete a Gloo resource
Options  -h, --help help for delete --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo glooctl delete proxy - delete a proxy glooctl delete upstream - delete an upstream glooctl delete virtualservice - delete a virtualservice  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl delete proxy</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_delete_proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_delete_proxy/</guid>
      <description> glooctl delete proxy delete a proxy
Synopsis usage: glooctl delete proxy [NAME] [&amp;ndash;namespace=namespace]
glooctl delete proxy [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for proxy  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  SEE ALSO  glooctl delete - Delete a Gloo resource  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl delete upstream</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_delete_upstream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_delete_upstream/</guid>
      <description> glooctl delete upstream delete an upstream
Synopsis usage: glooctl get upstream [NAME] [&amp;ndash;namespace=namespace]
glooctl delete upstream [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for upstream  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  SEE ALSO  glooctl delete - Delete a Gloo resource  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl delete virtualservice</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_delete_virtualservice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_delete_virtualservice/</guid>
      <description> glooctl delete virtualservice delete a virtualservice
Synopsis usage: glooctl delete virtualservice [NAME] [&amp;ndash;namespace=namespace]
glooctl delete virtualservice [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for virtualservice  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  SEE ALSO  glooctl delete - Delete a Gloo resource  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl get</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get/</guid>
      <description> glooctl get Display one or a list of Gloo resources
Synopsis Display one or a list of Gloo resources
Options  -h, --help help for get --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;) -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo glooctl get proxy - read a proxy or list proxies in a namespace glooctl get upstream - read an upstream or list upstreams in a namespace glooctl get virtualservice - read a virtualservice or list virtualservices in a namespace  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl get proxy</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get_proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get_proxy/</guid>
      <description> glooctl get proxy read a proxy or list proxies in a namespace
Synopsis usage: glooctl get proxy
glooctl get proxy [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for proxy  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;) -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  SEE ALSO  glooctl get - Display one or a list of Gloo resources  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl get upstream</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get_upstream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get_upstream/</guid>
      <description> glooctl get upstream read an upstream or list upstreams in a namespace
Synopsis usage: glooctl get upstream [NAME] [&amp;ndash;namespace=namespace] [-o FORMAT] [-o FORMAT]
glooctl get upstream [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for upstream  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;) -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  SEE ALSO  glooctl get - Display one or a list of Gloo resources  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl get virtualservice</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get_virtualservice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get_virtualservice/</guid>
      <description> glooctl get virtualservice read a virtualservice or list virtualservices in a namespace
Synopsis usage: glooctl get virtualservice [NAME] [&amp;ndash;namespace=namespace] [-o FORMAT]
glooctl get virtualservice [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for virtualservice  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;) -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  SEE ALSO  glooctl get - Display one or a list of Gloo resources glooctl get virtualservice route - get a list of routes for a given virtual service  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl get virtualservice route</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get_virtualservice_route/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_get_virtualservice_route/</guid>
      <description> glooctl get virtualservice route get a list of routes for a given virtual service
Synopsis usage: glooctl get virtualservice route
glooctl get virtualservice route [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for route  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;) -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  SEE ALSO  glooctl get virtualservice - read a virtualservice or list virtualservices in a namespace  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl install</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_install/</guid>
      <description> glooctl install install gloo on different platforms
Synopsis choose which version of Gloo to install.
Options  -h, --help help for install  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo glooctl install gateway - install the Gloo Gateway on kubernetes glooctl install ingress - install the Gloo Ingress Controller on kubernetes glooctl install knative - install Knative with Gloo on kubernetes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl install gateway</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_install_gateway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_install_gateway/</guid>
      <description> glooctl install gateway install the Gloo Gateway on kubernetes
Synopsis requires kubectl to be installed
glooctl install gateway [flags]  Options  -d, --dry-run Dump the raw installation yaml instead of applying it to kubernetes -f, --file string Install Gloo from this kubernetes manifest yaml file rather than from a release -h, --help help for gateway --release string install using this release version. defaults to the latest github release  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl install - install gloo on different platforms  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl install ingress</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_install_ingress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_install_ingress/</guid>
      <description> glooctl install ingress install the Gloo Ingress Controller on kubernetes
Synopsis requires kubectl to be installed
glooctl install ingress [flags]  Options  -d, --dry-run Dump the raw installation yaml instead of applying it to kubernetes -f, --file string Install Gloo from this kubernetes manifest yaml file rather than from a release -h, --help help for ingress --release string install using this release version. defaults to the latest github release  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl install - install gloo on different platforms  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl install knative</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_install_knative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_install_knative/</guid>
      <description>glooctl install knative install Knative with Gloo on kubernetes
Synopsis requires kubectl to be installed
glooctl install knative [flags]  Options  -d, --dry-run Dump the raw installation yaml instead of applying it to kubernetes -f, --file string Install Gloo from this kubernetes manifest yaml file rather than from a release -h, --help help for knative --knative-crds-manifest string Install Knative CRDs from this kubernetes manifest yaml file rather than from a release --knative-install-manifest string Install Knative Serving from this kubernetes manifest yaml file rather than from a release --release string install using this release version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl proxy</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy/</guid>
      <description> glooctl proxy interact with proxy instances managed by Gloo
Synopsis these commands can be used to interact directly with the Proxies Gloo is managing. They are useful for interacting with and debugging the proxies (Envoy instances) directly.
Options  -h, --help help for proxy -p, --name string the name of the proxy service/deployment to use (default &amp;quot;gateway-proxy&amp;quot;) --port string the name of the service port to connect to (default &amp;quot;http&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo glooctl proxy dump - dump Envoy config from one of the proxy instances glooctl proxy logs - dump Envoy logs from one of the proxy instancesNote: this will enable verbose logging on Envoy glooctl proxy stats - stats for one of the proxy instances glooctl proxy url - print the http endpoint for a proxy  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl proxy dump</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy_dump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy_dump/</guid>
      <description> glooctl proxy dump dump Envoy config from one of the proxy instances
Synopsis dump Envoy config from one of the proxy instances
glooctl proxy dump [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for dump -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode -p, --name string the name of the proxy service/deployment to use (default &amp;quot;gateway-proxy&amp;quot;) --port string the name of the service port to connect to (default &amp;quot;http&amp;quot;)  SEE ALSO  glooctl proxy - interact with proxy instances managed by Gloo  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl proxy logs</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy_logs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy_logs/</guid>
      <description> glooctl proxy logs dump Envoy logs from one of the proxy instancesNote: this will enable verbose logging on Envoy
Synopsis dump Envoy logs from one of the proxy instancesNote: this will enable verbose logging on Envoy
glooctl proxy logs [flags]  Options  -d, --debug enable debug logging on the proxy as part of this command (default true) -f, --follow enable debug logging on the proxy as part of this command -h, --help help for logs -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode -p, --name string the name of the proxy service/deployment to use (default &amp;quot;gateway-proxy&amp;quot;) --port string the name of the service port to connect to (default &amp;quot;http&amp;quot;)  SEE ALSO  glooctl proxy - interact with proxy instances managed by Gloo  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl proxy stats</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy_stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy_stats/</guid>
      <description> glooctl proxy stats stats for one of the proxy instances
Synopsis stats for one of the proxy instances
glooctl proxy stats [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for stats -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode -p, --name string the name of the proxy service/deployment to use (default &amp;quot;gateway-proxy&amp;quot;) --port string the name of the service port to connect to (default &amp;quot;http&amp;quot;)  SEE ALSO  glooctl proxy - interact with proxy instances managed by Gloo  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl proxy url</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy_url/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_proxy_url/</guid>
      <description>glooctl proxy url print the http endpoint for a proxy
Synopsis Use this command to view the HTTP URL of a Proxy reachable from outside the cluster. You can connect to this address from a host on the same network (such as the host machine, in the case of minikube/minishift).
glooctl proxy url [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for url -l, --local-cluster use when the target kubernetes cluster is running locally, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl remove</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_remove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_remove/</guid>
      <description> glooctl remove remove configuration items from a top-level Gloo resource
Synopsis remove configuration items from a top-level Gloo resource
Options  -h, --help help for remove --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo glooctl remove route - Remove a Route from a Virtual Service  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl remove route</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_remove_route/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_remove_route/</guid>
      <description>glooctl remove route Remove a Route from a Virtual Service
Synopsis Routes match patterns on requests and indicate the type of action to take when a proxy receives a matching request. Requests can be broken down into their Match and Action components. The order of routes within a Virtual Service matters. The first route in the virtual service that matches a given request will be selected for routing.
If no virtual service is specified for this command, glooctl add route will attempt to add it to a default virtualservice with domain &amp;lsquo;*&amp;lsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl route</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_route/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_route/</guid>
      <description> glooctl route subcommands for interacting with routes within virtual services
Synopsis subcommands for interacting with routes within virtual services
Options  -h, --help help for route --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo glooctl route sort - sort routes on an existing virtual service  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl route sort</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_route_sort/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_route_sort/</guid>
      <description> glooctl route sort sort routes on an existing virtual service
Synopsis The order of routes matters. A route is selected for a request based on the first matching route matcher in the virtual serivce&amp;rsquo;s list. sort automatically sorts the routes in the virtual service
Usage: glooctl route sort [--name virtual-service-name] [--namespace virtual-service-namespace]
glooctl route sort [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for sort -o, --output string output format: (yaml, json, table)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode --name string name of the resource to read or write -n, --namespace string namespace for reading or writing resources (default &amp;quot;gloo-system&amp;quot;)  SEE ALSO  glooctl route - subcommands for interacting with routes within virtual services  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl uninstall</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_uninstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_uninstall/</guid>
      <description> glooctl uninstall uninstall gloo
Synopsis uninstall gloo
glooctl uninstall [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for uninstall  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glooctl upgrade</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.8/cli/glooctl_upgrade/</guid>
      <description> glooctl upgrade upgrade glooctl binary
Synopsis upgrade glooctl binary
glooctl upgrade [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for upgrade --path string Desired path for your upgraded glooctl binary. Defaults to the location of your currently executing binary. --release string Which glooctl release to download. Specify a git tag corresponding to the desired version of glooctl. (default &amp;quot;latest&amp;quot;)  Options inherited from parent commands  -i, --interactive use interactive mode  SEE ALSO  glooctl - CLI for Gloo  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>