<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installing Gloo on Gloo Docs</title>
    <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.7/installation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installing Gloo on Gloo Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gloo.solo.io/0.7/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Gloo with Helm</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.7/installation/install_with_helm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.7/installation/install_with_helm/</guid>
      <description>This document outlines instructions for the setup and configuration of Gloo using Helm. This is the recommended install method for installing Gloo to your production environment as it offers rich customization to the Gloo control plane and the proxies Gloo manages.
Installation To install with Helm:
 Add the Gloo Helm repository:
helm repo add gloo https://storage.googleapis.com/solo-public-helm  (Optional) Customize the Gloo installation with a value-overrides.yaml file:
# example value-overrides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE)</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.7/installation/gke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.7/installation/gke/</guid>
      <description>In this document we will review how to install Gloo on Google Kubernetes Engine.
Configure kubectl Configure kubectl to use with your cluster:
gcloud container clusters get-credentials CLUSTER-NAME --zone ZONE --project PROJECRT_ID  Validate that kubectl was successfully configured with:
kubectl cluster-info  Install Gloo Use kubectl to install gloo using it&amp;rsquo;s released kubernetes manifest:
kubectl apply -f https://github.com/solo-io/gloo/releases/download/v0.6.19/gloo-gateway.yaml  In this example we are installing version 0.6.19. You can install any other released version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Production Deployment Using NodePort</title>
      <link>https://gloo.solo.io/0.7/installation/node_port/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gloo.solo.io/0.7/installation/node_port/</guid>
      <description>Motivation By default, micro-services deployed in kubernetes have an internal flat network that is not accessible from the outside of the cluster. This is true even if you use kuberentes on a public cloud (like Amazon AWs or Google Cloud).
A NodePort is a way to make kubernetes services available from outside the cluster (and potentially allow access from the internet).
In this document we will review how to expose Gloo via a NodePort.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>